(Sheldon:)Yeah, so the judges can give out
the prizes for best costume.
(Sheldon:)Most frightening, most authentic...
...most accurate visualization
of a scientific principle.
(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon, I'm sorry...
...but there aren't gonna be any parades
or judges or prizes.
(Sheldon:)This party is just going to suck.
No, come on, it's gonna be fun.
And you all look great.
(Penny:)I mean, look at you, Thor,
and, oh, Peter Pan.
(Penny:)That's so cute.
- Actually, Penny, he's Robin...
- I'm Peter Pan.
(Howard:)And I've got a handful of pixie dust
with your name on it.
(Penny:)No, you don't.
- Hey, what's Sheldon supposed to be?
- Oh, he's the Doppler effect.
(Sheldon:)Yes, it's the apparent change
in the frequency of a wave...
(Sheldon:)...caused by relative motion between
the source of the wave and the observer.
(Penny:)Oh, sure, I see it now.
The Doppler effect.
All right, I gotta shower. You guys,
um, make yourselves comfortable.